The venom of Cobra! The vengeance of Joe!
G.I. Joe: The Movie is a animation, action, science
fiction film directed by Don Jurwich.
Joe faces a new enemy as an ancient society of snake people known as Cobra-La try to
forcefully take back the earth from those who drove them underground eons ago.
Low-Light (voice), played by Charlie Adler.
Jinx (voice), played by Shuko Akune.
Wet-Suit (voice), played by Jack Angel.
Duke / Xamot / Blowtorch / Lift Ticket (voice), played by Michael Bell.
Motorviper (voice), played by Gregg Berger.
Taurus (voice), played by Earl Boen.
Joe: The Movie (also known as Action Force: The Movie in the UK) is a 1987 American direct-to-video animated
military science fiction  action film  produced as a sequel to the 1983 animated series G.I.
Joe: A Real American Hero, based on the original Hasbro toyline.
It was produced by Sunbow Productions and Marvel Productions and
was animated in Japan by Toei Animation Co., Ltd.
The film explores themes of army, mutation, battle
assignment, boot camp, based on toy.
The tone is thought_provoking.